Hi, I'm Madeline.
I'm Lulu.
I'm Eleanor.
I'm Olivia, and we're
the Chi O philanthropy chairs.
Chi Omega's philanthropy is Make-A-Wish.
Make-A-Wish is a nonprofit
organization that grants wishes
to children who have been
diagnosed with critical illnesses.
Over the years, our chapter
has donated over $400,000
and contributed 3,000 volunteer
hours to making wishes come true.
We host wish reveals right
here at our house where we
get to meet the children
whose wishes we're granting.
That's when you truly understand why
we put so much effort into this cause.
One of our biggest events
in the spring is Chi O Crawfish.
We get to host hundreds of people
from the community at our house,
have fresh crawfish
for everyone and a live band.
Every crawfish ticket sold directly impacts
a child's life in a real, tangible way.
That's the magic of Chi O Crawfish.
It's not just a fundraiser, it's
a community coming together to change lives.
Beyond Chi O Crawfish, we also
host a fall event that helps us
continue our fundraising and deepens
our connection with Make-A-Wish.
Every wish granted is a child that got
to experience joy when they needed it most
and a family that has
memories to hold on to.
Together, we're making wishes come true,
and that's what being
a Chi Omega is all about.
[Music]